<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Webcasts on tiagosalgado.com</title>
    <link>https://blog.tiagosalgado.com/tags/webcasts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Webcasts on tiagosalgado.com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 May 2010 00:04:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://blog.tiagosalgado.com/tags/webcasts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Visual Studio 2010 Technical Readiness Training</title>
      <link>https://blog.tiagosalgado.com/2010/05/18/visual-studio-2010-technical-readiness-training/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2010 00:04:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.tiagosalgado.com/2010/05/18/visual-studio-2010-technical-readiness-training/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#34;wlWriterHeaderFooter&#34; style=&#34;float:none; margin:0px; padding:4px 0px 4px 0px;&#34;&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1ª Sessão &amp;#8211; &lt;a href=&#34;https://msevents.microsoft.com/cui/WebCastEventDetails.aspx?EventID=1032452597&amp;amp;EventCategory=2&amp;amp;IO=fPTvWFAYtvc9YiS1DwDi8A%3d%3d&amp;amp;culture=en-US&amp;amp;CountryCode=US&#34;&gt;Visual Studio 2010 Tips &amp;amp; Tricks&lt;/a&gt; (20 de Maio de 2010)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this demo heavy tour, you will learn about out-of-the-box productivity features in Visual Studio 2010. Whether you&amp;#8217;re trying to come up to speed with an unfamiliar code base, navigate your way through a large solution, write in new pieces of business logic, or test your application, these tips and tricks will help you get your job done better and faster. Most demos will be in C# but we’ll also introduce some F# capability. If you are a developer using Visual Studio, this is the session to sit back, watch and enjoy!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2ª Sessão &amp;#8211; &lt;a href=&#34;https://msevents.microsoft.com/cui/WebCastEventDetails.aspx?EventID=1032452598&amp;amp;EventCategory=2&amp;amp;IO=fPTvWFAYtvecy2AWD9Gfeg%3d%3d&amp;amp;culture=en-US&amp;amp;CountryCode=US&#34;&gt;Visual Studio 2010 Architectural Tools&lt;/a&gt; (27 de Maio de 2010)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is an overview of the new Architecture capabilities available in Visual Studio 2010.&amp;#160; This new version of Visual Studio completely changes the architecture capabilities.&amp;#160; In addition to UML 2.0 compliant models, this session will demonstrate visualizing existing assets with architecture tools.&amp;#160; Tracing between other work items such as requirements and models will be shown as well as enforcement of layered architectures as part of the build process.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3ª Sessão &amp;#8211; &lt;a href=&#34;https://msevents.microsoft.com/cui/WebCastEventDetails.aspx?EventID=1032452599&amp;amp;EventCategory=2&amp;amp;IO=fPTvWFAYtvelIsyv1JZrNA%3d%3d&amp;amp;culture=en-US&amp;amp;CountryCode=US&#34;&gt;Improving Development Practices with Visual Studio 2010&lt;/a&gt; (3 de Junho de 2010)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is an overview of the new development in Visual Studio 2010. New capabilities of historical debugging, code analysis, profiling and the new test impact analysis will be demonstrated. Working with Team Foundation Server (TFS) 2010, gated-checkin will be discussed as well as the tester/developer collaboration experience. The new architect tools will be demonstrated to facilitate a better understanding of how modeling is a part of the development experience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;4ª Sessão &amp;#8211; &lt;a href=&#34;https://msevents.microsoft.com/cui/WebCastEventDetails.aspx?EventID=1032452600&amp;amp;EventCategory=2&amp;amp;IO=7UNzTMMofR1Sdsp0nReWJQ%3d%3d&amp;amp;culture=en-US&amp;amp;CountryCode=US&#34;&gt;Streamlining Testing with Visual Studio 2010 ALM Tools&lt;/a&gt; (10 de Junho de 2010)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This Visual Studio 2010 overview features Visual Studio Test Professional 2010 testing tools including using the new Microsoft Test and Lab Manager to manage and automate your UI testing. The use of Test Lab will be discussed as a means of automating the creation of virtual environments for testing purposes. Deploying to VM environments during build will be demonstrated and facilitate a robust developer/tester lifecycle. For a taste of real-world use, the test plans and test process used to perform multi-platform testing of Notion Tools for Team System will be shown.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Atenção que para cada sessão é necessário um registo.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Webcast4Share – Sharepoint e Enterprise Search</title>
      <link>https://blog.tiagosalgado.com/2009/03/16/webcast4share-sharepoint-e-enterprise-search/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2009 00:04:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.tiagosalgado.com/2009/03/16/webcast4share-sharepoint-e-enterprise-search/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Durante esta semana vai decorrer mais um ciclo de &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.microsoft.com/portugal/msdn/webcasts4share/default.mspx&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;webcast4share&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;18 de Março, 15h (Ricardo Calejo) – Como disponibilizar componentes de mapping com Sharepoint&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Como mostrar informação georeferenciada no Sharepoint&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Como utilizar o Sharepoint e o Virtual Earth para georeferenciar conteudos&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Como construir um componente de apresentação para estas funcionalidades&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;19 de Março, 15h (Luis Calado) – Sharepoint em cenários Internet&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Descrição das boas práticas de desenvolvimento&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Como responder a requisitos de compilance do HTML produzido no MOSS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Como integrar componentes de Silverlight em websites Sharepoint&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Como deve ser desenhado o processo de deployment das soluções desenvolvidas para Sharepoint e como devem ser asseguradas as passagens de desenvolvimento a produção&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;20 de Março, 15 (Luis Calado e Nuno Leitão) – Microsoft Enterprise Search&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enquadramento da plataforma Fast ESP na oferta de Enterprise Search da Microsoft&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Informações e registo no site &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.microsoft.com/portugal/msdn/webcasts4share/default.mspx&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;webcast4share&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>